Contact

713 705 2183 (Mobile) pgrami@me.com

www.linkedin.com/in/petragrami-dnp-rn-ccrn-ne-bc-cvrnbc-5b9ab010 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Critical Care Hospitals

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
German (Elementary)

Certifications

Critical Care Registered Nurse (CCRN)

Nurse Executive, Board Certified (NE-BC)

CardioVascular Registered Nurse (CVRN II)

Honors-Awards

Good Samaritan Nursing Excellence Bronze Award

20th Annual Nursing Celebration Nomination

Alan Fields Award

AACN, Innovative Research Award for 2015

Masters Award, Sigma Theta Tau International, Zeta Pi Chapter, 2015

Petra Grami DNP, RN, CCRN, NE-BC, CVRN BC

Director Specialty Units (ICU, EC, CDU, Obs. & Dialysis) at The University of Texas M.D. Anderson Cancer Center Houston, Texas

Summary

Experienced Nurse Leader that is innovative, energetic, and creative with a focus on achieving exceptional outcomes in a highly competitive, ever-changing environment that demands continuous improvement. Experienced in leading quality improvement teams, engaging staff, and customer service improvements. Emphasis in building relationships with peers, key physicians and community leaders. Exposure to research and research methodology. Core Practice Areas Include: Medical Surgical ICU, Cardiothoracic Surg ICU, Dialysis, Apheresis, Step down unit, Geratrics

Experience

MD Anderson Cancer Center
Director Speciality Units (ICU, EC, Obs. & Dialysis)
February 2019 - Present (1 year 4 months)

CHI St. Luke's Health - Baylor St. Luke's Medical Center 13 years 10 months

Nurse Manager Cardiothoracic Surgical ICU September 2017 - Present (2 years 9 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Nurse Manager, MSN, RN, CCRN, NE-BC, CVRN August 2006 - Present (13 years 10 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Baylor St. Luke's hospital is a 912-bed academic tertiary / quaternary Hospital in Houston Medical Center. Responsible for the all aspects of operations of a Thoracic Surgical ICU.

Several Hospitals From CNA, to LVN, RN, to Nurse Manager and CNO 1992 - 2009 (17 years)

Education

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth)

Doctorate of Nursing (DNP), Nursing Administration · (2017 - 2019)

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston Masters of Nursing, Leadership and Adminstration · (2014 - 2016)

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth)

BSN, Nursing · (1992 - 1994)